Planet Express crew,
report to headquarters immediately!
Repeat, what I just said, immediately!
- Sorry, Randy.
- Ah!
Step away from the car,
and no one gets hurt!
To the employment cave!
Oh.
Thanks, dear. Off to work.
Hya! Hya!
Whoa, whoa, there, girl.
Go on, now! Get on back to Paraguay!
We're being eaten by a giant spider!
There's no time for that!
The Professor needs us!
Uh, crew, as you know, I've delivered
a lot of good news in the past.
But what I'm about to lay down
is by far the greatest announcement
in the history of Planet Express!
What is it? I'm on the edge of my butt.
Ladies and gentlemen,
feast your eyes on our amazing new
soda machine!
That's what I'm talking about!
You undersold it, Professor!
Look, it has Slurm Loco!
It's the extreme-iest!
Hey, what can I get y'all?
Wow, you can talk?
Shut up and give me a Slurm Loco.
Ooh! Ooh!
Hey, drink machine,
what kind of alcoholic sodas you got?
Y'all can't drink at work!
This ain't a sawmill!
No alcohol? Pfft.
And you got the nerve
to call yourself a beverage machine?
I call myself Bev.
And if you're looking
for a smelly old can of booze,
go look in the mirror.
- Oh, snap.
- Oh!
No, no, everybody calm down.
Yeah, I need one more Slurm.
And one more to wash that
Slurm taste out of my mouth.
So I went to the bathroom,
and my pee was green. Pretty neat, huh?
I was wondering
who Shrekked in the toilet.
I hope you're proud of yourself, Bev.
You've turned this perfectly
worthless loser into an addict.
Cut me some slack, preacher.
I'm just a coal grinder's daughter
trying to stay off the pole.
With that big old caboose,
it'd have to be a telephone pole!
Hey-o!
Well, I guess a fellow's got to talk big
when he's sporting a little
shriveled up antenna like that.
What? You...
For your information, "Madam,"
it's a grower, not a shower!
My antenna's fine. It's just fine.
Ladies can't get enough Bender.
I need to loosen up.
Give me a screwdriver.
Hello. Who's your hot, dumb friend?
- Me?
Sure, why not.
Hang on. It's too bright in here.
Call me old-fashioned,
but I like a little romance in an orgy.
Let me switch off this weird light.
Ow!
Fry, it's 2:00 a.m.
What are you doing here
glowing on my skanks?
Just sitting here
turning quarters into urine.
We don't got to put up with this.
We got Poli Sci degrees.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Hang on.
I'll just politely escort him
to the gutter.
Scram, shiny!
All right, how we feeling?
Hot. I could bake a potato in my cleavage.
Yeah, I need a seltzer.
I'd be honored
to purchase you some refreshment.
Uh, hey, drink machine, you got anything
classy for these delicate flowers?
I ain't making drinks
for no trashy robo-sluts.
Trashy? At least
I don't put out for quarters.
Hey!
Hey. Stop that, drink machine.
Stop it, I say.
That's it, we're out of here.
Come on. We'll split a blintz.
Wait, give me a chance
to defend your honor
and then sully it on the couch.
All right, I've been waiting all day
for an excuse to hit a lady.
You try it, and I'll bash your face in.
Ooh! I'm so scared, No-Arms.
You want some of this?
- Interesting.
- Mmm!
Uh, Fry? You're glowing like
the Human Torch on prom night.
Shouldn't you be standing on a rocky coast
somewhere preventing shipwrecks?
Nice, hate me
because of the brightness of my skin.
You okay, ma'am?
I think your soda water broke.
My God! Bev just had a baby in my cup!
I know, right?
I better take that.
Aw. He's so cute. Wait. No, he isn't.
He looks like Bender!
Oh, no, no, no.
No way am I that kid's dad!
Wipe my tiny metal ass!
Ah, crap.
Mama, thirsty.
Hang on, dumpling. My milk's coming in.
Ugh. In public?
Aw, biscuits! I'm a father?
How did this happen?
Does this ring a bell?
Are you telling me
the stuff we did in private,
and also twice on the sidewalk,
made a baby robot? How?
Aw, Bender, didn't your mom ever tell you
where robot babies come from?
No. She was a religious fundamentalist.
Plus she didn't have a mouth.
It's an unusual combination.
Come on, everyone,
let's take Bender to the teen center
to learn about the bots and the bees!
It's okay, Bender.
No one here will laugh at you
for not knowing
where robot babies come from.
We don't know, either.
Then prepare to be embarrassed.
Or...
Meet Gerald, a maturing young robot.
Hey, he looks like me!
His hideous appearance is a by-product
of his hardware gearing up
for an important mission,
reproduction.
Oh, boy, oh, boy, oh, boy!
Since factories can't manufacture
enough robots to meet demand,
robots can also reproduce by mating.
Oh, now you tell me!
First, Gerald must find a female robot.
The best he can do is Francine.
After beer and hot wings
at a local gas station,
the two enjoy intimate time
behind a Dumpster.
It's all perfectly natural.
Let's watch, aroused,
as Gerald's antenna uploads a binary file
to Francine's internal drive.
Manufacturing specs
fromeach parent are then merged
by a randomized algorithm,
and the resulting code
guides assembly of a new robot.
Yes, everything your body does
is perfectly natural.
Except masturbation. That's just wrong.
Oh...
I can't believe I made a kid!
I'm not ready!
There's so much of the world
I haven't stolen yet!
Relax, Bender.
No one would let you near a child.
Bev will get custody,
and you'll be a deadbeat dad
who never even bothers
to know his own son.
You really think so?
I know so.
You're absolutely horrible in every way.
You're sweet, Leela.
Sorry, Bev,
but I ain't cut out for fatherhood.
So here's my certificate of abandonment
drawn up by our notary.
That'll be 10 bucks.
Now take your kid
and hit the soup line!
Oh, no, you don't, mister!
Damn baby's driving me crazy!
He won't stop giggling
no matter how much I scream at him!
There, there.
I still got womanly needs!
Who's gonna look twice at me with this
dirty leech hanging off my dairy nozzle?
Not me, that's for sure.
Then it's settled! He's all yours, Pappy!
Hey, wait! You can't leave... What?
Ah... Ah!
What the...
Can't I have
one moment to myself?
Why can't you sleep?
I left my window open, and moths got in.
I swear, if I wasn't such a great dad,
I'd grab
his ugly little neck and...
Hey, he stopped screaming for a second!
Bend some other stuff!
Ah!
Bend! Bend!
He loves bending, just like me.
Aw, I'm gonna call him Ben,
after the first half of me, Bender.
That's my bastard.
Whoo-hoo!
Bend it, Daddy!
Bend it like it called you poo-poo-face!
It called me what?
Yay! You bended it like a pretzel.
Okay, now you.
I can't do it!
Hey, buddy, you're learning.
You'll get there.
Bender, I was wrong.
You're a fine parent, and I want to...
- Leela was wrong!
Daddy, how'd you get so good at bending?
I inherited my arm control software
from my mom.
That's how it's passed down,
mother to son.
But my mommy had no arms!
Does that mean I can never be a bender?
Well, sure you can! You just need
to get a bending card installed.
I hate to crush a boy's dreams,
but what the heck.
He has only one expansion slot,
and it holds his memory card.
This robot will never bend.
Don't tell my son
what he can and can't do!
You may know what's in his head,
but you don't know what's in his heart!
There's no slot in there, either.
I said shut up!
Today marks
young Ben's thirteenth day
of being left on continuously.
And so, before the Lord
and this congregation,
we upgrade him to man-bot.
Can I get a mazel tov?
Mazel tov!
I'd like to thank
the preacher-bot for the introduction
and also for not circumcising
me again, am I right?
Twice was enough. But seriously,
today, I'm not just a man-bot,
I'm the luckiest man-bot alive.
My mom may have abandoned me,
but I have the greatest dad
in the whole universe.
He's patient,
he's not afraid to show his emotions...
Don't look at me!
...and someday, if my dreams come true,
I'll be a bender, just like him.
You must be so proud of your boy.
I could take him or leave him.
I'm back for my son!
I've come to take him and leave with him!
She beat you to both things!
It's okay, Son, Mama's here now.
Daddy! Don't let her take me!
Get your lack of hands off my boy!
You're an unfit parent
who abandoned her child!
Oh, yeah?
Well, I'm still less unfitter than you.
Says who?
Says this document you gave me
when you tried to abandon Ben first!
It's genuine.
That doesn't prove I'm an unfit parent!
I was drunk and violent
when I signed that!
Well, I'm drunk and violent now.
He's coming with me!
Daddy!
Son!
My boy's gone.
All I have left to remember him
are these innocent playthings
we stole together.
Fry, put these someplace safe.
That's it, Fry!
For a guy who's not too bright,
you're too damn bright!
Now, get out! And don't come back
until someone finds a use
for a million-watt idiot!
Mom, will I ever get to see Dad again?
No, he died yesterday.
Rust monsters ate his face.
Sweet dreams!
Psst! Quit whimpering
or you don't get kidnapped.
Dad!
Oh... Come on. Let's run for it.
What's going to happen to us now, Dad?
Well, I reckon we'll just sit around
this campfire a while.
But then what?
Only a fool plans
more than a few centuries ahead, Son.
Freeze, tin woodsman!
You're under arrest for kidnapping
and burning raccoons without a permit!
- It's over, Dad.
- It ain't over!
I can't outrun a hovercopter,
but I can out-bend it!
I know! Let's outrun it!
- There's a dam!
- Damn!
There's a grate!
- Great!
- But I can't bend anything
with my arms agonizingly maimed like this.
Well, maybe I can!
You can do it, Son.
Yeah, this ain't gonna happen.
Is that even necessary?
I'm sorry, Daddy.
You got nothing to be sorry about.
He's really
a very good father.
All right, I got her statement.
And a straight-up grape soda.
Aw, yeah.
I promise
things will be different, Son.
From now on,
I'm chaining you to a radiator.
I'm amazed someone who dispenses
such warm soda could be so coldhearted!
I'm gonna buy a drink
just so I can throw it in your face!
It's another soda baby!
Oh...
Damn.
You got knocked up by a police officer
while he was looking
for your kidnapped child?
Sure did! I still got it.
So, now what happens?
Tell you what, you keep the big one.
Long as I got a baby to neglect,
I'm happy.
Should we call child services?
No, let's just get outta here.
Whoo-hoo!
Whoo! Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Whoo?
Sorry, Dad. I'm glad to be back.
I'm just kind of bummed
I can't bend stuff.
All I ever wanted was
to go to Bending State-Santa Cruz.
But that's never gonna happen.
Listen, you need something bent,
you come to me, huh, champ?
Damn it, I love that little guy so much!
I'd sacrifice any four of you
if it would help him bend even a little!
There is one way,
but no, it's too horrible.
Nothing's too horrible for my boy!
Well, I could install a bending card.
But you said he only has one slot!
Correct. I'd have to remove
his memory card.
He'd be able to bend,
but he'd lose all his memories.
He wouldn't even remember who you are.
You sure you want to be a bender, Son?
More than anything.
Just remember, your daddy loves you.
Remember that, will you, Son?
Remember that.
Dad, are you crying?
No! I said with the mouth
you're looking at.
You sure
take after your old man!
I never knew my father.
Ooh!
It's not important.
What is important is that we get you
to Bending State-Santa Cruz
in time for registration.
Then we'd better hurry.
Registration ends in one hour.
To the ship!
Ugh.
It's too foggy.
We can't navigate through this storm.
Our lights aren't bright enough.
I'm sorry I let you down, Son.
Who are you again?
It's just not possible to get you
to bending school this year.
Or is there?
All right, Fry!
Merry college registration day, everyone!